[
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "Ø¬Ù†ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§Œ",
        "response": "Ù‚Ø²Ù…"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§™",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ø­Ø±"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸ«",
        "response": "Ù…Ø¯Ø±Ø³"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ•µï¸",
        "response": "Ù…Ø­Ù‚Ù‚"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¾",
        "response": "Ù„Ø¹Ø¨Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«˜",
        "response": "Ø­Ø¨ÙˆØ¨"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒ½",
        "response": "Ø°Ø±Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸƒ",
        "response": "ÙŠÙ‚ØªÙŠÙ†"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¬",
        "response": "Ù…ØµØ±"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«€",
        "response": "Ù‚Ù„Ø¨"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘ƒ",
        "response": "Ø§Ù†Ù"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘€",
        "response": "Ø¹ÙŠÙˆÙ†"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜·",
        "response": "Ù…Ø±ÙŠØ¶"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘»",
        "response": "Ø´Ø¨Ø­"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤–",
        "response": "Ø±ÙˆØ¨ÙˆØª"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™»ï¸",
        "response": "Ø§Ø¹Ø§Ø¯Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ–Œï¸",
        "response": "Ù‚Ù„Ù…"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‚",
        "response": "Ù…Ù„Ø­"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ´â€â˜ ï¸",
        "response": "Ù‚Ø±Ø§ØµÙ†Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš–ï¸",
        "response": "Ø¹Ø¯Ø§Ù„Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§²",
        "response": "Ù…ØºÙ†Ø·ÙŠØ³"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¬",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆÙ…Ù†Øª"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ””",
        "response": "Ø¬Ø±Ø³"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ–±ï¸",
        "response": "ÙØ§Ø±"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ‚ï¸",
        "response": "Ù…Ù‚Øµ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›±ï¸",
        "response": "Ø´Ù…Ø³ÙŠÙ‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ›¸",
        "response": "Ù…Ø±ÙƒØ¨Ù‡ ÙØ¶Ø§Ø¦ÙŠÙ‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”’",
        "response": "Ù‚ÙÙ„"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§",
        "response": "Ø³Ù…Ø§Ø¹Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ—‘ï¸",
        "response": "Ø³Ù„Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‘",
        "response": "ØªØ§Ø¬"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ‰ï¸",
        "response": "Ø¸Ø±Ù"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§¸",
        "response": "Ø¯Ù…ÙŠÙ‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ—ï¸",
        "response": "Ù…ÙØªØ§Ø­"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦š",
        "response": "Ø·Ø§ÙˆØ³"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŸ",
        "response": "Ø³Ù…ÙƒÙ‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš°ï¸",
        "response": "Ù‚Ø¨Ø±"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦",
        "response": "Ø³Ø­Ù„ÙŠÙ‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸªœ",
        "response": "Ø³Ù„Ù…"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù…Ø§Ø³"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¿",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³Ø·ÙˆØ§Ù†Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¡",
        "response": "Ù„Ù…Ø¨Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "âŒš",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ø¹Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ•‹",
        "response": "ÙƒØ¹Ø¨Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›º",
        "response": "Ø®ÙŠÙ…Ù‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ ",
        "response": "Ù…Ù†Ø²Ù„"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”ï¸",
        "response": "Ø¬Ø¨Ù„"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›„",
        "response": "Ø±Ø¬Ù„ Ø«Ù„Ø¬"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸŒ¸",
        "response": "ÙˆØ±Ø¯Ù‡"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸš",
        "response": "ØµØ¯ÙÙ‡"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ø±"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ§",
        "response": "Ø¨Ø·Ø±ÙŠÙ‚"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¶",
        "response": "ÙƒÙ„Ø¨"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜•",
        "response": "Ù‚Ù‡ÙˆÙ‡"
    },
    {
       "question": "âš¡",
        "response": "Ø¨Ø±Ù‚"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜ï¸",
        "response": "Ø³Ø­Ø§Ø¨"
    },
    {
       "question": "âœ¨",
        "response": "Ù†Ø¬ÙˆÙ…"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸŒ‹",
        "response": "Ø¨Ø±ÙƒØ§Ù†"
    },
    {
       "question": "âœˆï¸",
        "response": "Ø·ÙŠØ§Ø±Ù‡"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸš€",
        "response": "ØµØ§Ø±ÙˆØ®"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ’°",
        "response": "ÙÙ„ÙˆØ³"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¥š",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙŠØ¶Ù‡"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ—¿",
        "response": "ØµÙ†Ù…"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¦",
        "response": "Ø­Ù…Ø§Ù…Ù‡"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¤",
       "response": "ÙƒØªÙƒÙˆØª"
}
]
